<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ace Trace - mobile golf shot traccker</title>
    <link>https://acetrace.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ace Trace - mobile golf shot traccker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:03:42 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acetrace.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace Tutorial for iOS</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/tutorial-ios-version-7/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 13 Oct 2023 11:03:42 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/tutorial-ios-version-7/</guid>
      <description>Version 7.0 and higher Ace Trace has been completely redesigned for iOS in version 7.0. Here is our new tutorial. You can also always look at the old tutorial for additional insights.
Automatic golf ball tracking with Ace Trace If your shot was filmed in good light conditions and from a proper angle behind the golfer, you should give the automatic tracking a shot! It&amp;rsquo;s easy and fast, and it works in most cases.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Exploring the Advent of Golf Visualization &amp; Its Benefits for High Performance Gameplay</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/exploring-the-advent-of-golf-visualization-and-its-benefits-for-high-performance-gameplay/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 02 Sep 2023 11:55:03 +0200</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/exploring-the-advent-of-golf-visualization-and-its-benefits-for-high-performance-gameplay/</guid>
      <description>Golf is 10% movement and 90% psychological, according to renowned golfer Arnold Palmer: the cumulative duration of the golfer&#39;s swings and ball strikes over the 72 holes amounts to around seven minutes and 30 seconds, resulting in a remaining duration of 15 hours, 52 minutes, and 30 seconds designated for cognitive processes and decision-making.
Yet, what does this 90% entail? How does one harness the mind&#39;s immense potential to improve their game on the green?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Tutorial Acetrace Golf and Disc Golf</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/tutorial-acetrace-golf-and-disc-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 14 Jul 2023 17:52:42 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/tutorial-acetrace-golf-and-disc-golf/</guid>
      <description>Table of Contents Introduction Free Curve Importing a video Manual tracing Trace Golf Importing a video Automatic tracking Manual tracking Line Settings Distance Counter Color segments Introduction Ace Trace is a powerful yet simple tool to trace trajectories on your mobile device and create video highlights like in professional tournament coverage of your favorite sport.
You can trace any kind of object; however, the app is optimized mostly for two main activities - golf and disc golf.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tracking ML Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/disc-and-golf-ball-automatic-tracking-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/disc-and-golf-ball-automatic-tracking-feature/</guid>
      <description>Golf has always been a precision sport, and thanks to contemporary technology, players can now raise the bar on their abilities.
Our cutting-edge machine learning (ML) tracking algorithm enables our newest feature, automatic tracking for discs and golf balls in movies.
Challenges Unfortunately, standard ML detection approaches are not well-suited for detecting and tracking small objects like golf balls.
Due to the limitations of deep learning neural networks, it is challenging to extract characteristics about objects that are only a few pixels in diameter.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of shot tracking apps</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 11:41:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</guid>
      <description>Golf ball tracking technology has revolutionized the way golfers analyze their shots and improve their game. With the ability to track the ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory, speed, and spin in real-time, golfers can now gain a deeper understanding of their shots and make the necessary adjustments to take their game to the next level. One of the key benefits of using a golf ball tracking app is the ability to save and analyze data on previous shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf shot tracing apps review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</guid>
      <description>There are a few different apps available on the AppStore for golf ball tracking
Ace Trace Shot Tracer / Golf Shot Tracer - the same app, but two different names The Golf Tracer Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they compare to each other.
Tracing All tracers&amp;rsquo; main feature is highlighting the golf ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory by tracing its flight path and drawing a line.
Automatic tracking Some tracers offer the automatic option that automatically allows tracing the ball trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace release notes</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/releases/2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/releases/2-1/</guid>
      <description>2.7 Redesigned the preview screen 2.5 Made cursor and the line transparent during drag&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;drop and video scrolling 2.3 Added double-tap gesture to reset zoom/cursor position Bug fixes 2.1 New design No plus button - just move the cursor to update the line Quicker access to the distance editor - the icon in the toolbar 2.0 Purchase options Made sign-in optional Added video bundle purchase options Added free videos New features Allowed to only select certain photos for access Fixed zooming in the editor Allowed to add points outside of the video viewport Added the width gradient setting Redesigned settings and preferences panels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/help-leave-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/help-leave-message/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/privacy2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/privacy2/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy When you first use Ace Trace, we ask you for access to your photo library so we can read your videos and modify them. Video data is extremely sensitive, and we believe it’s important for you to know and understand what we do with that data.
We firmly believe that your data belongs to you. As such, Ace Trace does not collect, store, or share any videos, or data that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/schedule-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/schedule-call/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/terms2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/terms2/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions Introduction Please read these Terms of Service (“Terms”) carefully as they contain the legal terms and conditions that you agree to when you use the video editing services provided to you by Ace Trace service, provided through Ace Trace, or co-branded retailer sites (collectively, the “Service”). By using our Service you agree to be bound by these terms. Part A: Provisions applicable to all Users of the Service (Whether Registered or Not)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/tutorial/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace at MVP Open 2022</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/mvp-open-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/mvp-open-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ace Trace is on sale for the MVP Open! Get a 15% off of the annual subscription during the disc golf tournament The offer has expired, but you can still get the Ace Trace! Get Ace Trace Saturday Traces A preview of Saturday drives on hole 1 MPO View this post on Instagram A post shared by Ace Trace (@acetrace.app)
View this post on Instagram A post shared by Ace Trace (@acetrace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace community</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/community/</guid>
      <description>Chat with us We welcome you to join our Discord Chat for the fastest communication. Please, share your ideas and ask questions! We&amp;rsquo;re always ready to listen to your feedback. It&amp;rsquo;s also the best place for you to pioneer some of our experimental features.
Leave feedback Another way to communicate your feedback is using the form or by email
Help us make it better No matter what your skills are, if you want to help, we will be always glad if you joined our humble team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace end user license agreement</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/terms/</guid>
      <description>Last updated December 28, 2022
Ace Trace™ is licensed to You (End-User) by Ivkin LLC, a Massachusetts limited liability company dba &amp;ldquo;Ace Trace App&amp;rdquo;, for use only under the terms of this License Agreement.
By downloading the Application from the Apple AppStore or Google Play store, and any update thereto (as permitted by this License Agreement), You indicate that You agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of this License Agreement and that You accept this License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace F.A.Q.</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/faq/</guid>
      <description>F.A.Q. How do I trace a line? Free Curve - manual editing You can mark a few points in manual mode, and the app will create a smooth line using them.
Scroll the video to find the object Select the object by moving the cursor. You can zoom in with 2 fingers Scroll the video again and mark the object by moving the cursor Add 4 to 10 key points throughout the flight Tap [Preview] to preview the result Trace Golf Scroll the timeline to the beginning of the flight, try to be precise Select the ball with the cursor Wait for the automatic tracking to complete - it&amp;rsquo;s just a few seconds Adjust the landing point by moving the cursor Change the flight duration by moving the marker in the timeline Tap [Preview] button to see the result Check out the iOS Golf tutorial for the tracing golf shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace golf and disc golf tutorial</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-acetrace-golf-and-disc-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-acetrace-golf-and-disc-golf/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace golf tutorial</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-golf/</guid>
      <description>Automatic tracking with Ace Trace It works with ball golf drive videos filmed with the camera behind the ball, and the ball moving away from the camera.
Make sure the ball is fully visible in the video, so our cutting edge ML algorithm can detect it.
Start by opening a video Scroll the timeline to the beginning of the flight, try to be precise Select the ball with the cursor Wait for the automatic tracking to complete - it&amp;rsquo;s just a few seconds Adjust the landing point by moving the cursor Change the flight duration by moving the marker in the timeline Tap [Preview] button to see the result You can save your video by tapping the [Save] icon on the preview screen Manual tracking If for some reasons the automatic tracking doesn&amp;rsquo;t produce the best results, you can always use the manual tracking mode.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace Maple Hill</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/maplehill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/maplehill/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations, you found me! Let&amp;rsquo;s create awesome highlights You can put your phone in the holder, and use me for filing your throw. Upload your video and we&amp;rsquo;ll add a line folling your disc to it.
Can you match the line? You have a chance to compete with other disc golfers, trying to repeat a shot made by a pro. We will put your and the reference line in the same video, so you&amp;rsquo;ll see the double ace trace line for yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace on Android</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/android/</guid>
      <description>The good news - the Ace Trace app is available for Android. Currently, the Free Curve and Golf editing modes are fully supported. The golf mode has fully functioning automatic tracking! You can start tracing your lines immediately.
Check it out!
While we are actively developing new features!
Stay tuned.
Limitations of the app on the Android platform Android Only specific (standard) video dimensions work due to Android video codec limitations Video stabilization is slightly slower on Android due to the inability to read a video file in several parallel threads, unlike iOS.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace privacy policy</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Last updated December 28, 2022
This privacy notice for Ivkin LLC (&amp;quot;Company,&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share (&amp;quot;process&amp;quot;) your information when you use our services (&amp;quot;Services&amp;quot;), such as when you:
Visit our website at https://acetrace.app, or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice
Download and use our mobile application (Ace Trace), or any other application of ours that links to this privacy notice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tracking</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/annotation-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/annotation-task/</guid>
      <description>Cannot wait for the automatic tracking feature to come alive? Have free time and a computer? You’re patient and careful for details? We would like to offer you an opportunity to significantly help the project. As a reward you will get a lifetime Premium Ace Trace subscription free of charge or the money equivalent.
Cannot help with automatic tracking, but still want to be a part of the Ace Trace community?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Download Ace Trace</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/appstore/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/appstore/</guid>
      <description>On your mobile phone or a tablet Ace Trace is available for iOS, iPadOS and Android. Make sure to open this page on your mobile device.
App features vary depending on the platform.
Desktop version The desktop version is under development. If you are interested in participating in the beta testing, please contact us.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/feedback-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/feedback-ios/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/feedback/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf shot tracing apps review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/shot-tracing-apps-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/shot-tracing-apps-review/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/golf-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/golf-review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subscribed</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/subscriptionconfirmation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/subscriptionconfirmation/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re all set. Cannot wait to email you the good news!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
