<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Ace Trace - golf shot tracker</title>
    <link>https://acetrace.app/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Ace Trace - golf shot tracker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 11:41:39 -0500</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acetrace.app/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of shot tracking apps</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 11:41:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</guid>
      <description>Golf ball tracking technology has revolutionized the way golfers analyze their shots and improve their game. With the ability to track the ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory, speed, and spin in real-time, golfers can now gain a deeper understanding of their shots and make the necessary adjustments to take their game to the next level. One of the key benefits of using a golf ball tracking app is the ability to save and analyze data on previous shots.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf shot tracing apps review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</guid>
      <description>There are a few different apps available on the AppStore for golf ball tracking
Ace Trace Shot Tracer / Golf Shot Tracer - the same app, but two different names The Golf Tracer Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they compare to each other.
Tracing All tracers&amp;rsquo; main feature is highlighting the golf ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory by tracing its flight path and drawing a line.
Automatic tracking Some tracers offer the automatic option that automatically allows tracing the ball trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace release notes</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/releases/2-1/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 30 May 2022 17:02:29 -0400</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/releases/2-1/</guid>
      <description>2.7 Redesigned the preview screen 2.5 Made cursor and the line transparent during drag&amp;rsquo;n&amp;rsquo;drop and video scrolling 2.3 Added double-tap gesture to reset zoom/cursor position Bug fixes 2.1 New design No plus button - just move the cursor to update the line Quicker access to the distance editor - the icon in the toolbar 2.0 Purchase options Made sign-in optional Added video bundle purchase options Added free videos New features Allowed to only select certain photos for access Fixed zooming in the editor Allowed to add points outside of the video viewport Added the width gradient setting Redesigned settings and preferences panels </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/help-leave-message/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/help-leave-message/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/privacy/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/privacy/</guid>
      <description>Privacy policy Last updated December 28, 2022
This privacy notice for Ivkin LLC (&amp;quot;Company,&amp;quot; &amp;ldquo;we,&amp;rdquo; &amp;ldquo;us,&amp;rdquo; or &amp;ldquo;our&amp;rdquo;), describes how and why we might collect, store, use, and/or share (&amp;quot;process&amp;quot;) your information when you use our services (&amp;quot;Services&amp;quot;), such as when you:
Visit our website at https://acetrace.app, or any website of ours that links to this privacy notice
Download and use our mobile application (Ace Trace), or any other application of ours that links to this privacy notice</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/privacy2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/privacy2/</guid>
      <description>Privacy Policy When you first use Ace Trace, we ask you for access to your photo library so we can read your videos and modify them. Video data is extremely sensitive, and we believe it’s important for you to know and understand what we do with that data.
We firmly believe that your data belongs to you. As such, Ace Trace does not collect, store, or share any videos, or data that can be used to identify or contact a specific individual.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/schedule-call/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/schedule-call/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/terms/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/terms/</guid>
      <description>END USER LICENSE AGREEMENT Last updated December 28, 2022
Ace Trace™ is licensed to You (End-User) by Ivkin LLC, a Massachusetts limited liability company dba &amp;ldquo;Ace Trace App&amp;rdquo;, for use only under the terms of this License Agreement.
By downloading the Application from the Apple AppStore or Google Play store, and any update thereto (as permitted by this License Agreement), You indicate that You agree to be bound by all of the terms and conditions of this License Agreement and that You accept this License Agreement.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/terms2/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/terms2/</guid>
      <description>Terms and Conditions Introduction Please read these Terms of Service (“Terms”) carefully as they contain the legal terms and conditions that you agree to when you use the video editing services provided to you by Ace Trace service, provided through Ace Trace, or co-branded retailer sites (collectively, the “Service”). By using our Service you agree to be bound by these terms. Part A: Provisions applicable to all Users of the Service (Whether Registered or Not)</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-golf/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/tutorial-golf/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/tutorial/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/tutorial/</guid>
      <description> </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace at MVP Open 2022</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/mvp-open-2022/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/mvp-open-2022/</guid>
      <description>Ace Trace is on sale for the MVP Open! Get a 15% off of the annual subscription during the disc golf tournament The offer has expired, but you can still get the Ace Trace! Get Ace Trace Saturday Traces A preview of Saturday drives on hole 1 MPO View this post on Instagram A post shared by Ace Trace (@acetrace.app)
View this post on Instagram A post shared by Ace Trace (@acetrace.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace community</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/community/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/community/</guid>
      <description>Chat with us We welcome you to join our Discord Chat for the fastest communication. Please, share your ideas and ask questions! We&amp;rsquo;re always ready to listen to your feedback. It&amp;rsquo;s also the best place for you to pioneer some of our experimental features.
Leave feedback Another way to communicate your feedback is using the form or by email
Help us make it better No matter what your skills are, if you want to help, we will be always glad if you joined our humble team.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace F.A.Q.</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/faq/</guid>
      <description>F.A.Q. How do I trace a line? Free Curve - manual editing You can mark a few points in manual mode, and the app will create a smooth line using them.
Scroll the video to find the object Select the object by moving the cursor. You can zoom in with 2 fingers Scroll the video again and mark the object by moving the cursor Add 4 to 10 key points throughout the flight Tap Preview to preview the result Disc Golf - automatic tracking Scroll to the beginning of the flight Select a disc by the rectangular frame Tap the Start Tracking button Trace Golf Scroll the video to find the start of the flight Select the ball by moving the cursor Adjust the landing point by moving the yellow ring Adjust the shape of the trajectory by moving control points Change the flight duration by resizing the bar in the timeline Adjust the acceleration - make the opaque line end match the current frame ball position Can Ace Trace track it automatically?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace Maple Hill</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/maplehill/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/maplehill/</guid>
      <description>Congratulations, you found me! Let&amp;rsquo;s create awesome highlights You can put your phone in the holder, and use me for filing your throw. Upload your video and we&amp;rsquo;ll add a line folling your disc to it.
Can you match the line? You have a chance to compete with other disc golfers, trying to repeat a shot made by a pro. We will put your and the reference line in the same video, so you&amp;rsquo;ll see the double ace trace line for yourself!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Ace Trace on Android</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/android/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/android/</guid>
      <description>The good news - the Ace Trace app is available for Android. Currently, the Free Curve editing mode is fully supported. You can start tracing your lines immediately, and there is one free video for everyone.
Check it out!
While we are actively developing new features, they are most likely to first appear on the iOS. However, we are maintaining and continually improving the Android app as well.
Stay tuned.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tracking</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/annotation-task/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/annotation-task/</guid>
      <description>Cannot wait for the automatic tracking feature to come alive? Have free time and a computer? You’re patient and careful for details? We would like to offer you an opportunity to significantly help the project. As a reward you will get a lifetime Premium Ace Trace subscription free of charge or the money equivalent.
Cannot help with automatic tracking, but still want to be a part of the Ace Trace community?</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/feedback-ios/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/feedback-ios/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Feedback</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/feedback/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/feedback/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf shot tracing apps review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/shot-tracing-apps-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/shot-tracing-apps-review/</guid>
      <description>There are a few different apps available on the AppStore for golf ball tracking
Ace Trace Shot Tracer / Golf Shot Tracer - the same app, but two different names The Golf Tracer Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they compare to each other.
Tracing All tracers&amp;rsquo; main feature is highlighting the golf ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory by tracing its flight path and drawing a line.
Automatic tracking Some tracers offer the automatic option that automatically allows tracing the ball trajectory.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/review/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/review/</guid>
      <description>&lt;!DOCTYPE html&gt; </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Subscribed</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/subscriptionconfirmation/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/subscriptionconfirmation/</guid>
      <description>You&amp;rsquo;re all set. Cannot wait to email you the good news!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
