<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blogs on Ace Trace - mobile golf shot tracker</title>
    <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blogs on Ace Trace - mobile golf shot tracker</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://acetrace.app/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Automatic Tracking ML Algorithm</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/disc-and-golf-ball-automatic-tracking-feature/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 02 Apr 2023 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/disc-and-golf-ball-automatic-tracking-feature/</guid>
      
        <description>Golf has always been a precision sport, and thanks to contemporary technology, players can now raise the bar on their abilities.
Our cutting-edge machine learning (ML) tracking algorithm enables our newest feature, automatic tracking for discs and golf balls in movies.
Challenges Unfortunately, standard ML detection approaches are not well-suited for detecting and tracking small objects like golf balls.
Due to the limitations of deep learning neural networks, it is challenging to extract characteristics about objects that are only a few pixels in diameter.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Benefits of shot tracking apps</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 05 Feb 2023 11:41:39 -0500</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/benefits-of-shot-tracking-apps/</guid>
      
        <description>Golf ball tracking technology has revolutionized the way golfers analyze their shots and improve their game. With the ability to track the ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory, speed, and spin in real-time, golfers can now gain a deeper understanding of their shots and make the necessary adjustments to take their game to the next level. One of the key benefits of using a golf ball tracking app is the ability to save and analyze data on previous shots.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Golf shot tracing apps review</title>
      <link>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 20 Sep 2022 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://acetrace.app/blog/shot-tracing-apps-review/</guid>
      
        <description>There are a few different apps available on the AppStore for golf ball tracking
Ace Trace Shot Tracer / Golf Shot Tracer - the same app, but two different names The Golf Tracer Let&amp;rsquo;s see how they compare to each other.
Tracing All tracers&amp;rsquo; main feature is highlighting the golf ball&amp;rsquo;s trajectory by tracing its flight path and drawing a line.
Automatic tracking Some tracers offer the automatic option that automatically allows tracing the ball trajectory.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>